thesixfigurementors.com 2012-05-05

# Privacy Policy | Welcome to The Six Figure Mentors

This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for the website that linked you here. We will notify you of changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new policy on this website. Review our Privacy Policy regularly so that you can stay informed of our current practices, as they may change in the future.

By using our services or submitting information, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Your assent to these practices is essential for us to provide our services. Similarly, we need you to provide accurate personal information so that you can be contacted and use our website and related services. You can opt-out and decide not to provide the requested personal information. However, by doing so, we will not be able to contact you and you will not be able to use our website and/or services.

The personal information we collect includes name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, user name, and password. Other personal information that you may submit is clearly labeled at the time you submit it. We use the information that we collect to provide our services, to contact you regarding our products and services, and to improve our site. We also share your name, address, telephone number, and other contact details with the member, if any, who referred you to our website. Once a third-party obtains your personal information, its subsequent use is controlled by their business practices, which is beyond our control. By providing us a telephone number and/or email address, you are expressly requesting that we and/or anyone to whom we subsequently share or transfer your personal information contact you at that number or email address. Note, however, that your payment information is used only for order processing purposes.

We automatically collect certain information from visitors to, and members of, the site, such as Internet addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring and exit page, operating system, timestamps, and clickstream data. We also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, and to administer our site so that we can constantly improve the quality of the services we provide.

When you pay for anything on our site using a credit or debit card—including your monthly membership fee—we collect the personal information needed to complete the transaction. This information includes your name, card number, and other necessary information, all of which is clearly labeled on the form you use to submit payment. We use an unaffiliated, credit card processing company to process your payment. We transfer your payment information—and you authorize us to do so—to this company solely for this purpose. The company does not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

Anything you send us, post on our site, or use with our service, such as emails or voice recordings, or if other users or third parties send us anything about your activities or postings, we will collect such information into a file specific to you. We use information in the file that we maintain for you, and other information that we obtain from your use of the services, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, and enforce our membership agreements.

Contact us at the address below if you want us to change or delete any information that we have about you. We will respond to your request to access, update, or delete your information within ten (10) business days. Before we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies, or delete any information, however, we may ask you to verify your identity.

This website is owned and operated by:  
Empowered Marketing Ltd
